André Arakelyan

An expert in quantitative analysis, predictive modeling, and systematic trading based out of Luxembourg. After studying general management at a top 2 German private business school, Mr. Arakelyan worked in management consulting for CFOs of large corporations listed in Germany (DAX), consulted ultra-high-net-worth individuals on digital assets, and finally worked as a trader for a Swiss multi-family-office with \$3 billion in assets under management where he was responsible for introducing and managing the emerging asset class of Digital Assets.

Experience

Research Analyst at Theta-Digital Luxembourg Sarl-s

Capellen, Luxembourg

Investment Research

- Building institutional grade digital asset model portfolios for UHNWI clients and family offices
- · Performing quantitative empirical research on liquidity and scalability of digital asset portfolios

Junior Portfolio Manager at Corecam AG

Vienna, Austria

2019 - present

2018

Swiss Multi-Family Office (\$3bn AUM)

- Responsible for overseeing a \$10mm portfolio of Digital Assets at a leading investment advisor for entrepreneurs, large families, foundations, and companies in Europe and Asia
- Generated in-house market research and created custom valuation models

Management Consultant

Wiesbaden, Germany

Undisclosed Family Office (\$100mm AUM)

2017

sets

Consulted management of a UHNW family office client on portfolio integration of Digital Assets

Strategic Management Consulting at KPMG

Frankfurt, Germany

CFO & CIO Consulting for large corporations (DAX)

Digital Transformation, Blockchain

- Digital Transformation, Dio
- Technology Roadmap
- Enterprise Architecture planning, governance, and development

Risk Analyst at SmartStone Capital

Frankfurt, Germany

2016

2016

Student led investment club

Analysed different trading strategies with the view to improving the risk-return profile

Head of Research at EBS.Invest e.V.

Frankfurt, Germany

2015 - 2016

- Student led investment society (80 members)
- · Organized and held finance, investing, and trading workshops for fellow students
- Lead a team of 15 student analysts & traders to manage the fund's portfolio
- Charity campaign: donated all profits to support local social projects

Head of IT at James Consulting GmbH

Frankfurt, Germany

2015

- Student led consulting firm
- Organized a research project for a London based hedge fund (\$25bn AUM)
- Supervised a state-of-the-art internal IT system

Workshops Frankfurt, Germany

Deutsche Bank (Global Markets), Nomura (Investment Banking Division), PWC (Strategy&)

2015 - 2016

Education

European Business School (EBS Universität für Wirtschaft und Recht)

Oestrich-Winkel, Germany

2017

Focus: Asset Management

Extracurriculars: TEDxEBS, EBS.Invest e.V., James Consulting GmbH

Undergraduate Studies in General Management, TOP 2 University in Germany

Max-Planck-Gymnasium

Trier, Germany

2014

German Abitur (Baccalaureate, science focus)

Focus: Mathematics, Politico-economic studies, Biology